THE APARTMENT JOB
Mr. Park. I'm sorry.
but I can't work here anymore.
You can't just quit like this.
You fired me suddenly too.
You already received your payment.
You should do your job.
What's the point in being your wife
for two more weeks?
You already got the position
that you wanted so badly.
Our family still needs you. Ms. Kang.
Mr. Park. that family you speak of
is fake anyway!
What?
"Fake"?
Oh. my goodness. You…
So you guys…
were a fake family?
I see.
My gosh. I get it now.
I did think it was strange.
Those guys were telling their father
they'd cut off his hands.
and you were telling the boy
to call you Ha-ri.
I was wondering
what kind of messed-up family you were.
So that's why.
Everything was fake.
Fake?
You misheard.
I said. "Take."
I told her we needed to
take it easy on the salt.
Right. honey.
The kimchi stew was pretty salty.
-It was salty.
-Yeah. it was.
It was salty.
Enough about the stew.
I heard it clearly with my own ears.
"That family you speak of is fake anyway!"
You misheard!
That's nonsense.
-Why would we fake a family?
-Right.
Why would you do that?
But you should know
that this is a serious matter.
You've deceived
this entire apartment complex.
you understand?
Ms. Jang. that's not--
But…
why did you go to such lengths
to become the president?
What are you scheming?
What are you up to?
-No. wait. Forget it.
-Ms. Jang…
President Park… I mean. Mr. Park.
You…
should step down immediately.
I can't just let this slide.
I'm going to post this
on our community forum.
-Move aside.
-It's under maintenance.
Darn it. This stupid elevator
is always out of order.
You frauds.
Ms. Jang…
Emergency!
Ms. Jang just found out
that we're a fake family.
What?
She just said
she's going to post this online.
We have to stop her.
What's going on?
Why isn't the internet working?
What's wrong with this apartment?
And why is the elevator
stuck on the 29th floor?
I can't hold on any longer.
Gosh.
What?
I'm sorry. ma'am.
It's not opening. Geez.
What's going on?
Darn it!
This stupid apartment!
I've had it with this place!
It must smell nice
because it's from France.
It's my first time using hand lotion.
You didn't need to get me a gift.
It's a farewell gift. Mr. Choi.
You scare me whenever you say that.
I told you several times.
And President Seo
also asked me to continue
just until the end of his term.
So you returned when you heard
the president had changed?
Yes.
President Seo
is in a tight spot
because he lost the election.
None of us expected him
to lose that position.
I'll talk to him
when the timing is right.
so please stay until then.
Without you here. our apartment complex
will be in huge trouble.
Ha-jeong.
It was a misunderstanding earlier.
Our company's client asked me
to look after their son.
Why would a lawyer
visit a client's house to do such work?
And he called you "Mom."
I had no choice. I'm just a newbie.
I have to do as I'm told.
And he loves me more than his mom.
He just calls me "Mom" sometimes.
You studied hard to become a lawyer.
It upsets me
to see you running errands like that.
Well. I told them I can't do it anymore.
But why did you return so early?
Your trip was supposed to last longer.
Something came up at work.
You should've told me
so I could be prepared.
Prepared for what?
I mean. I would've picked you up
from the airport.
Give me that. It must be heavy.
How was France?
It was nice. but I did miss spicy food.
That's a tacky way
to flaunt that you were abroad.
You remember. right?
First encounter. library
First kiss. under a street light
Fateful encounter
At a book club after-party
We checked that Ms. Jang went home
after struggling with the door last night.
She'll come out
for her morning exercise soon.
Okay. got it.
Since it's an emergency.
I'll allow a wide range of touching.
She's coming.
Honey. hurry up.
Careful not to get hurt. honey.
You can protect me.
I do protect you. don't I?
-Shall we go?
-Yes.
Gosh.
I can tell that you're faking it.
It's so obvious.
Married couples
don't run around holding hands.
Geez.
We used to be in a book club.
I fell in love with her at first sight
at a library.
Our first kiss was under a street light.
Our first kiss…
I don't want to know.
I'm not curious at all.
I don't want to hear it!
-Ms. Jang!
One week.
Can't you just wait one week?
One week?
What are you planning to do
during that week?
Can't you give me a chance
to win back your trust?
Don't you remember this place?
Cut!
That was soulless.
Why is your tone so cold?
You need to express more sincerity. Again!
Sincerity.
Do you remember this place?
You and I stood here together
and shouted ourselves hoarse
for a common goal.
That glorious memory
of our struggle paying off
is still engraved deep in my heart.
All right. fine.
That was a happy memory for me too.
Our housing prices rose thanks to that.
I do admire you for it.
But you must have
some reason to fake a family
to become the president…
…of the residents' association!
I'm telling you. we're not a fake family.
I really…
love my wife.
Sure. you do.
You have to sincerely believe it
when you say you love your wife. Again!
Right.
I really love my wife.
I love her!
I love her! With gestures too!
-I love her!
Gestures! I love her!
I love her!
I love my wife.
I married her because I love her.
and we even had a child.
I didn't want to tell you this.
but my brothers
all have different mothers.
Gosh. All three of them?
My father had
a rather scandalous life in his youth.
Right. I did think it was strange.
You didn't look anything alike.
What's more…
my father started gambling. so…
Oh. dear.
We were so scarred because of him.
but we were living together
to mend our relationship.
Right. I see.
-Oh. dear.
-Nice.
Fine. let's say that's true.
However…
from all the data I've collected so far.
you guys are very suspicious.
I have a bad feeling about you.
That's why I'm asking you
to make your judgment after one week.
It won't be too late to decide then.
I didn't want to bring this up.
but the maintenance fees
you're always complaining about…
What?
What about the maintenance fees?
I think there's an issue with them.
To be honest. I was investigating it.
You were investigating that matter?
You should've told me.
So that's what you were doing.
All right. fine.
Then I'll give you just one week.
That's it.
One week.
THE APARTMENT JOB
Boss.
How did it go?
We have one more week.
We have to find the fund
within a week and flee.
The Lizard. Bring him here.
-Right.
-Lizard.
I've been thinking about it.
And?
I've racked my brains.
but let's say the facility manager.
the accounting manager.
and the president teamed up
and pocketed the fund.
But even so.
they wouldn't have emptied out
the entire account like this.
You've been the president for a few days.
so you'd know.
Apartment complexes
have fixed monthly expenses.
and unexpected emergency costs
come up all the time.
Emptying out the entire account
makes no sense.
What's your point?
There must be someone behind this.
What?
There are three major methods
to pocket the fund.
First is to manipulate the books
and skim off a little at a time.
The second is to inflate
the construction costs. pay it out.
then get a kickback from the contractor.
Then the third is to just say.
"Screw it" and spend the money.
Which method did you use?
I mixed all three methods. of course.
Anyway. none of these methods
would result
in an entirely empty bank account.
Why? There can't be any problems
with emergency spending
for you to pocket the money
without getting caught.
That means someone powerful
is backing them.
So there's someone behind the scenes
controlling the reserve fund?
Who?
How would I know?
-Bring the bag.
-It's in my closet.
-Should we go up to the roof again?
-Wait.
It might help you think.
There's a way to find out.
Use the fund with your position.
Whether it's construction or whatever.
make something up
that requires you to use the fund.
But if the construction proceeds
when the account is empty.
that means the money was paid
and someone paid the contractor.
It would cost quite a lot.
Will there be any issues using the fund?
Not at all.
This is exactly what
the reserve fund is for.
We don't have time.
Find anything that can be paid for
out of the reserve fund.
-Yes. Boss!
Don't let a single tile or nail
go unchecked.
Check things that look fine too.
Starting tomorrow.
we're making sure this place
is under constant construction.
-Let's find…
-Defects!
Let's find some…
The drains are way too open.
They need to be open!
Over here.
We can do crack repairs here.
See? I told you there were a lot.
-There's one here!
-There's one here too!
I found one here too.
That's a selfie.
It's leaking!
A leak repair.
Lizard. this one's a different color.
What's with this?
It's the design.
-What is it?
-I just tripped on a block. Right here.
Hello.
The new president is working really hard.
Yeah. I'm glad he got elected.
-Yeah. He's doing a great job.
-He is.
Why is he working so hard?
Great job. everyone.
Let's enjoy our lunch.
-Yes. sir.
You put all of these in?
How do you make a profit?
I want an Italian BMT sandwich
on grain bread.
creamy egg salad with extra avocado.
meat. pepperoni. and cheese.
For the sauce. sweet low-sugar onion.
tangy red wine vinegar
and a sprinkle of salt.
-What will you have?
-Just have one.
It's one sandwich.
Really?
I want one with meat.
Stop. We'll all order the same one.
Steak and cheese. please.
This is really tasty.
What is this? It's so good.
This will keep me full until dinner.
This is perfect for a man my age too.
We did find things
to spend the reserve fund on.
but what do we do now. Mr. Park?
We need to move.
FACILITY MANAGER
Mr. Choi. we need
a building rep meeting immediately.
Our apartment complex is a mess.
Let's tackle the issues one by one.
EMERGENCY MEETING
ORGANIZER: PARK HAE-KANG
All right.
Hello.
I'm President Park Hae-kang of True Value.
I called this emergency meeting today
because there are several
urgent matters to address.
It's been about six years
since residents moved in.
so we're starting to see problems
popping up here and there.
So first.
I'd like to repair
the cracks in the parking lot.
This must be done
with the long-term repair reserve fund.
Excuse me.
The parking lot floor is completely fine.
You might not know
since you're new to the job.
but you can't just use the fund
recklessly like that.
I'm not suggesting we use it recklessly.
I've been told we can use
the reserve fund for this
since it's for facility replacement
and repairs.
Just because it's possible
doesn't mean this repair is necessary.
Are you saying
that we can just tear apart
or replace things that are perfectly fine
as long as the fund covers it?
I checked the apartment complex
here and there.
and it wasn't perfectly fine.
There are chips and scrapes everywhere.
Construction is absolutely necessary.
We should hold off as long as we can.
You shouldn't waste
the reserve fund like this.
Waste?
It's his first time as president.
He's just clueless about his job.
Then let's put this to a vote.
Who here agrees to repairing the cracks
in the parking lot?
All right. Those who oppose?
The second item on the agenda
is repairing the leak in the machine room.
Who agrees to using the reserve fund?
Who opposes?
What? Everyone's opposing.
And replacing the pavement blocks.
Who here opposes?
Why isn't he asking who agrees?
Because it's too obvious.
I knew it. I told you this would happen.
Fourth item on the agenda.
Who here opposes
repainting the buildings' exterior?
Next. replacing the tiles and fixing
the floor in the community center.
Who here opposes?
Replacing the automatic
fire detection system.
Who opposes?
All right. Thank you. everyone.
Why is everyone opposed
to what Uncle says?
Uncle Hae-kang doesn't have
his own connections there.
That's how harsh the world is.
People take sides
and want their team to win
while the other loses.
This is bad for your education.
Then we'll wrap up True Value's
building representative meeting.
Thank you.
Seo Gang-won is doing a good job.
Everyone opposed.
Our new president
is bold enough to plant relics.
What will he do now?
I'm pretty sure he won't just sit back.
Sir.
We got a call from the head of Hansu Bank.
Why?
True Value's
residents' association president
came to withdraw the entire reserve fund.
What?
He would've found out
that the account is empty.
Mr. Kim.
I get it now.
I get why Park Hae-kang
wanted to become the president.
What's the reason?
The reserve fund.
He became the president
to pocket the fund.
I never imagined that would be the reason.
He found out it was empty.
so he's trying to use the fund.
I'm so excited right now.
I'm going to lose my mind.
I'm getting a dopamine rush!
What's with those building reps?
Why are they opposing everything?
I feel like they're not helping
with the association's matters at all.
Don't I have the authority to remove them?
The building reps
are elected by the residents.
so unless they're accused of corruption.
you can't dismiss them.
They're standing in the way
of improving this place.
That's basically corruption.
Sir.
Over there.
She's our accounting manager.
Let's say the facility manager.
the accounting manager
and the president teamed up
and pocketed the fund.
But even so.
they wouldn't have emptied out
the entire account like this.
The accounting manager.
You didn't get to meet
since she was on vacation.
Ha-jeong. this is the president.
I've been wanting to meet you.
Hello. I'm Kang Ha-jeong.
I'm Park Hae-kang. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
We'll have a lot
to discuss together from now on.
We will?
We can talk next time.
I'm heading out.
I guess our apartment complex
is changing now.
A man who lives alone
became the president.
He doesn't live alone.
He has a huge family.
Do you live alone?
Why? Is there a problem with that?
Was it a different guy?
Park Hae-kang will have no choice
but to step down.
He would have realized today
-that he can't do whatever he wants.
-Exactly.
He must've been feeling pretty high
and mighty about becoming the president.
-It's so satisfying.
-Totally.
He'll learn
that popularity doesn't mean much.
Once Park Hae-kang steps down.
you should return to your position.
Absolutely.
I think that's the thing about the world.
This is nice and sweet.
Things tend to follow…
their natural course.
Of course.
Why are they against
using the reserve fund?
Calm down. Mr. Park.
I'd have to be crazy
to be lying to you in this situation.
You're giving me food. shelter
and clothes right now.
-So?
-Gosh.
You saw earlier
how President Seo's supporters
are still groveling.
That means President Seo
is still handing out kickbacks.
-Kickbacks?
-Yeah.
Even after Mr. Park became the president.
those assholes
are still clinging to President Seo
and sucking up to him.
Why would they do that?
Because there's still
something in it for them.
If I ask you what that is.
you'll just tell me
to figure it out myself.
How did you know?
Wanna sleep in that bag again?
How long will you threaten me with this?
Isn't there anything new?
Don't take it out on me.
You should be dealing with
President Seo's bootlickers.
You guys look into the building reps
supporting President Seo.
We don't have much time.
We have to find whatever we can
and get rid of them to use the fund
and find where it went.
President Seo and those bootlickers…
I'll crush them to pieces.
Did you forget the basics
of digging into people?
Yes. I'm heading out.
The font is so small.
Hey. look at the bills.
Why are you looking at food?
I can't find anything noteworthy.
Maybe we've lost our touch.
I'll look through them again.
We can't use the reserve fund
while President Seo still holds power.
We have to take them out first.
I'm here.
What is all this?
Why do you have other people's bills here?
Why is their heating bill zero?
This one's zero too.
And this one?
Wait. How can all of them be zero?
What is it?
What's with these houses?
-Their heating bills are zero.
-What?
What is it? Let me see.
That can't be possible.
Does this make any sense?
Over 100 households?
Precisely 123 households
have a heating bill of zero.
We've checked that they're paying
for their water bills and parking.
but it's just the heating bill
that's zero.
These are the households
with zero heating bills.
They're the building representatives.
including President Seo's
closest supporters.
There are even
former building representatives.
Ever since President Seo
formed the association.
he's been the president all these years.
So all of his supporters
have zero heating bills.
That's right.
The accounts that wrote
malicious comments about you
are the same as those
that have zero heating bills.
So he even ran a troll farm.
These guys have obviously
been doing this for a long time.
He formed the association
about six years ago. didn't he?
Then they could've paid
zero heating bills for six years.
So he gave them kickbacks through this.
But if 123 households
haven't been paying their heating fees.
then who was paying for them?
The other 9.000…
So the other 9.677 households
were paying for theirs.
That's right.
But they won't even know
that they're paying for them.
This is just ridiculous.
No one found out about this for six years?
Shouldn't we report this to the media?
Report this?
Yes. that's right.
We can make them step down
as building representatives
if we make this public.
Right! Your brain works well
in situations like this.
Then you could eliminate everyone
who's against you all at once.
Yes.
Then will you become
another Heating Bill Martyr?
What?
Don't you know the Heating Bill Martyr?
The most famous martyr
besides independence fighters
is the Heating Bill Martyr.
Heating Bill Martyr…
PARK HAE-KANG IS HERE
TO PROTECT YOUR HEATING BILL!
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR HEATING BILL CORRUPTION!
They're going totally overboard.
Everyone. what kind of people are we?
We are a resilient people
who roamed the Manchurian Plains.
spread our gallantry across the world
and stood united
against foreign invasions and crises.
I am standing here now with the spirit
of the independence fighters
who gave everything to resist
during our nation's biggest crisis.
Everyone.
A total of 123 households
have not paid any heating bills
for six whole years.
I discovered this fact!
Those 123 households
have been enjoying free heating
thanks to someone's abuse of power.
Zero heating bills?
Yes. Ms. Senior Secretary.
I could not remain silent
in the face of such abuse of power.
I promise to expose
all the hidden corruption
within this apartment complex
and fight…
against these illegal acts!
Everyone!
Heating Bill Martyr!
Problem-solver Park Hae-kang!
Pay your heating bills!
We should all pay our heating bills!
I will solve this problem. everyone.
The former president and building reps
weren't paying their heating bills.
Shouldn't we catch those thieves first?
Those jerks took our money.
All the other households
were paying for their heating bills.
This is so unfair.
This isn't mismanagement. It's fraud.
Did we elect these people
as representatives
just so they could rip us off?
Don't make excuses. Take responsibility.
We will not let this slide.
Wait.
I was a mathematics major.
Let's say the average heating bill
for a 112-square-meter house in winter
is about 200.000 won.
Then it'll be one million
over five months.
and six million over six years.
There's also hot water usage
for spring. summer. and fall.
Then let's say it's about
ten million in total.
But there are 123 households.
so it's 1.23 billion.
1.23 billion?
This shall be known as the "123 Incident."
We weren't aware of this.
We'll be checking all 123 households.
We can't check all the bills
for each household every month.
Don't worry. Please just wait…
Yes. I'm sorry.
We sincerely apologize.
All right.
We had no idea.
You have to play dumb. no matter what.
This is the management office.
What do we do now?
Park Hae-kang just had to meddle again.
It seems like
he's doing everything he can to annoy us.
We should've stopped him
from getting elected. no matter what.
You're right.
What do we do?
The online forum is in an uproar.
Sir. please say something.
Well…
just insist that we didn't know…
the gas meter was broken.
What can they do if we say we didn't know?
Would that work. though?
Then should we just admit
that the building reps
and some residents
who wrote comments for us
received zero heating bills until now?
Should I just tell the truth?
Should we all go down together?
You've been enjoying the benefits
for a long time.
Use your brains…
to think. will you?
Just use your brains.
Can't you think?
Your penthouse also had zero heating bills
for the past six years.
It seems President Seo
was overly loyal to you.
It looks like Seo Gang-won
was busy doing something interesting.
The other 122 households
were close to President Seo
or had some kind of connection.
Gang-won is quite bold. isn't he?
He did something
I didn't even tell him to do.
What on earth was he thinking?
Excuse me. sir.
LEE SANG-GYU. GONGYEONG DAILY PRESIDENT
-I think you should take this. sir.
-All right.
Hello. How have you been?
I was about to give you a call.
You're low on fuel. aren't you?
Why don't we fill it up?
Mr. Kim.
Let's use the reserve fund.
"Relics discovered at Oman New Town site…
found to be fabricated.
Planned by a group
opposing the new town project."
Isn't that a nice scenario?
Give him a full tank.
A sedan for Gongyeong Daily…
and a fruit box for the online media.
The dream of owning a home
has been delayed again.
YouTubers have a large influence
on public opinion these days.
so let's grease some palms there too.
How will they fill
the housing supply target of 70.000 units?
Send something sweet.
So why? Who is trying
to stop the new town project?
Planting relics at the site?
Mr. Kim.
We spent a huge sum today. haven't we?
I'm sure the media will move
after using all that money.
And you spent three billion
on Hyeonpo Apartment last year.
but there's an audit soon.
What will you do?
The apartment complex in Soyeong-dong.
How much is left in that reserve fund?
We're using that fund too.
so there's a little over six billion left.
I should use that then.
You know.
whenever I use the reserve fund
from an apartment complex.
I feel like a kid raiding a piggy bank
without telling Dad.
But Dad doesn't have a clue.
Just like the residents.
What excuse will they come up with
for not paying the heating bill?
It's obvious.
They'll say the gas meter was broken.
but they had no clue.
It's always the same excuse.
It doesn't matter what they say.
We just have to check
if the reserve fund is being disbursed.
You're sure gas meter replacements
are done with the reserve fund?
Yes. It's different
for every apartment complex.
but. fortunately.
it's stated in the regulations.
-You'd better be sure.
-I am.
And we can use this chance to wipe out
President Seo's faction in one go.
TRUE VALUE STATE
123 INCIDENT HEARING
Do you think we're running a charity?
This should be front-page news!
I just can't believe this!
How could you do this to all of us?
I will step down
and return to being an ordinary resident
of True Value--
Are you kidding me?
Stepping down won't solve anything!
You think that will make it okay?
We need to report this to the police.
We need to request an audit
and figure out exactly what happened.
down to every last detail.
Don't you agree?
-You're right!
-Yes!
I mean…
Honestly. I don't get
why you're blaming everything on us.
Our gas meters were broken.
What were we supposed to do?
Do you all just stare
at your gas meters every day?
Even if you didn't see your gas meter.
you would've seen your bill.
You had zero heating bills
in the middle of winter.
How could you not know
for six whole years?
Six years!
Do you hear what he's saying?
He's supposed to be a building rep!
-Ridiculous.
-Building reps are people too!
Sometimes we're too busy
to check our bills.
I set up automatic payments.
so I don't check them sometimes.
Automatic payments?
Are we not people too?
Are you kidding me? "Automatic payments"?
This is just nonsense. Hey.
Even so. this is strange.
Why did this happen
only to the building representatives?
That's exactly what I mean.
And we mothers really can't understand
how the facility manager
didn't know about this for six years.
It's your job to oversee this. Mr. Choi.
Mr. Choi. come over here.
Say something. Come over here.
-Tell us.
-Just tell us everything.
What happened?
Just explain everything.
I…
Well…
This is infuriating.
I have nothing to say.
I'm really sorry.
Mr. Choi. I'm disappointed in you.
I had no idea he was that kind of person.
Unbelievable.
Calm down. everyone!
I understand how you feel.
but this has already happened.
so we must figure out how to resolve this.
The most urgent matter
is to replace the broken gas meters.
-With the reserve fund--
-But…
Yes?
Why would you use
the reserve fund for that?
The management regulations
state that gas meter replacements
should be done with the reserve fund.
So I'll take care of that issue
according to the regulations.
Is there something you'd like to say?
I live on the top floor of Building 123.
It turns out that
I had zero heating bills as well.
I wasn't aware.
I don't check the gas meter or my bills.
I know it may sound irresponsible
to say I didn't know.
but I agree with
what the building reps are saying.
There was something going on with him too.
That is why
I will pay for all the heating bills
I haven't paid for until now.
Wouldn't it only be right
for all the building reps
to do the same?
Wait.
This wasn't our fault.
Why should we pay for everything--
Well. you've found out now.
so you should pay your bills.
The heating bills that you haven't paid
have been paid
by all the other residents so far.
You should at least be feeling sorry.
We're all neighbors.
-He's right.
-Right.
Everyone.
The man living in the penthouse
really is different.
They say generosity comes from money.
but he also seems to have a conscience.
That's very admirable.
You're so cool.
-You're cool!
-Very admirable.
Mr. Seo.
What do you think?
Me? I…
Mr. Seo.
Well. I…
Since you asked for my opinion.
I also believe we should pay
for all the heating bills.
-President Seo.
What are you saying?
Of course.
Of course. they should pay their bills.
All right. That's great.
Then now.
I'll recheck all the households
that had zero heating bills
and collect all the fees
that they haven't paid.
And I'll make sure
to distribute the collected fees
to the remaining 9.677 households
who have had to pay extra until now.
You're amazing!
We love you!
President Park.
You seemed as wise as King Solomon today.
"Recover the unjust gains
and distribute them equally
to the people."
That was so cool.
I was more impressed by your words.
In any case. thank you.
Keep up the good work. President Park.
Bye.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
I was curious what kind of people
lived in penthouses.
Mr. Lee?
He's very humble and cool.
unlike many rich people.
-You know him?
-When did you start admiring him?
Since the moment we saw him.
Anyone rich is admirable.
Great job. President Park.
-Thank you.
-We're rooting for you.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
You did a decent job today.
But…
don't let your guard down.
I'm keeping an eye on you.
Good job today. guys. See you later.
-Bye.
-Bye. Ms. Senior Secretary.
Get home safely. ma'am.
You should lose some weight.
Mr. Kim.
Have you seen Spider-Man?
Yes. a long time ago.
"With great power
comes great responsibility."
The famous quote?
Yes.
It's time for Seo Gang-won
to take responsibility.
I gave him power over 9.800 households.
but he gave birth
to a heating bill martyr.
Will you invite Gang-won
on a date with me?
Yes. sir.
Were you all notified?
-About the 123 Incident heating bills?
-Yes.
We'll each get an equal share
of the fees paid by the 123 households.
I heard they'll deduct that amount
from this month's maintenance fee.
I should pay more attention
to my maintenance bill from now on.
Me too.
I never paid attention
since it's paid from my husband's account.
In any case.
isn't our president
really good at his job?
He's handsome. and he's so capable.
I know. right?
These days. I've been watching
all the residents' association meetings.
It's like I'm watching a celebrity.
He does seem a bit different.
I can sense his passion.
What he did regarding the heating bills
was pretty touching.
The way he exposed the 123 Incident
and even resolved the issue…
I feel so relieved
that our residents' association president
is someone like him.
-True.
-You're right.
Totally. I'm so happy.
Yes!
Let's have beer next time.
How about some beer?
PRESIDENT PARK HAE-KANG
Yes?
You're here. Ms. Senior Secretary.
Come and sit down.
You said you needed a week.
Was that…
so you could take care
of the 123 Incident?
It was an urgent matter.
I already have so much to do.
That you do.
But…
would a week be enough. President Park?
What?
Goodbye. Ms. Senior Secretary.
With great power
comes great responsibility.
Sir.
Yes?
It's me. sir.
I know you must be busy.
but I wanted to ask
when I should come pick up the money.
Come in two hours.
All right.
This is premium Italian hardwood flooring.
They said it was resistant to cracking.
Mr. Kim. I think it's cracked.
It seems like you hit the floor
a little too hard with the golf club.
But it doesn't really show.
Really?
Damn it.
My 300-million-won floor
almost got ruined because of you.
Can't you hear me?
Seo Gang-won.
Wake up. Seo Gang-won!
Seo Gang-won!
You can't just die like this.
Don't you know how much I lost?
You should've served your purpose
until the end.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes. sir.
We should move him
to Taegowon.
Be careful.
TAEGOWON
All right!
Thinking back on it.
you really didn't have anything to offer.
You weren't capable.
and you weren't even funny either.
So why don't you
become fertilizer for this mountain…
and take good care…
of our baby trees now?
Take good care of them.
Where the hell is he going?
Something's fishy.
He's going inside.
-Did you take it?
-Yes.
"Tae…" What is it?
"Taegowon."
-Taegowon?
-Yes.
What is this place?
SEO GANG-WON
Hello.
You arrived just in time.
Yes. sir.
-Mr. Kim. give him the money.
-Yes. sir.
I don't get
how Park Hae-kang found out.
-I'm sorry. sir.
-No. it's fine.
It was quite amusing.
I swear I won't let it happen again--
Don't.
Pardon?
I'm enjoying this.
so just let Park Hae-kang
do what he wants.
Yes. sir.
Since you're here.
you should pay your respects.
All right.
Here.
Former President Seo Gang-won's…
tree.
This is the tree that will grow
with Seo Gang-won's flesh and blood.
Let's pay our respects.
May you live a long life.
He's back.
Take photos.
That's a bag of cash.
Cash?
Taegowon?
The facility manager tripped.
and that bag was filled
with 50.000 won bills.
Did any other employees
do anything suspicious?
Besides the facility manager.
everyone else is working late.
And they're replacing
the gas meters tomorrow?
Yes. sir.
Then the facility manager
must have gotten the money for that.
I did a search.
and Taegowon is a tree farm.
They mostly sell trees
used for apartment landscaping.
A tree farm?
TAESAN PARK
TAESAN CONSTRUCTION. TAESAN PLANT…
TS NETWORKS
Taegowon is owned by TS Networks.
It's a real estate development company.
one of Taesan Construction's affiliates.
And TS Networks
is True Value's developer.
while Taesan Construction
is the construction company.
TAESAN CONSTRUCTION
That means Taesan is behind all this.
Would they even see us?
Boss.
Huh?
Places like this won't see you
without an appointment.
Just let me give it a try.
Hello.
Please inform the president
that True Value's
residents' association president
is here to see them.
He's waiting for you. sir.
-What?
-Please follow me.
It wasn't me.
…46. 47. 48. 49. 50. 51. 52.
That's 52 points.
with pibak. gwangbak. meongtta.
a shake. a three-go and a four-go.
so it'll be 342.800 won.
If someone's winning over 300.000 won
in a 100-won-a-point game.
it's no longer just a game.
That's gambling.
Have you been visiting gambling dens?
Go-Stop is all about momentum.
Momentum.
Come on.
Even if we're a fake family.
I'm still your father-in-law.
Ha-ri.
At least give me a discount.
Hang on. Hello?
Hello. I'm Gyeong-buk's teacher
from the Stanford Class.
Gyeong-buk seems to have a bit of a fever.
What? Gyeong-buk has a fever?
Please make sure everything goes smoothly.
All right.
The gas meter replacements
will be done by today.
Great work. everyone.
We're not getting
any more calls from the residents.
We can finally get some rest.
Everyone's happy that
their maintenance fees will be reduced
with the recovered heating charges.
Why don't we have lunch together
to celebrate?
Yes!
We can recharge
and get our spirits back up.
Sure. Everyone worked hard.
It's lunchtime. Let's go.
-Yes. sir.
-Awesome.
Aren't you joining us. Ms. Kang?
I'm not feeling well.
Come with us. Ha-jeong.
You worked the hardest.
Come on.
-Come on. you scared me.
-Hey.
-Don't eat that.
-Sorry.
Boss. she said
the president was waiting for us.
Isn't that strange?
Maybe we were being followed.
It feels like they set a trap.
knowing we were coming.
What took you so long. President Park?
I've been waiting for you all this time.
Come inside.
Let us talk. president to president.
Come on. Watch your step.
Boss…
PHARMACY
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
Let's go.
This isn't something to say
to a kindergartener.
but you should take care of your own body.
Being sick only hurts yourself.
No one can suffer in your place.
Not your dad or your uncles.
Okay.
Mom…
I mean. Ha-ri.
Can't you carry my bag today?
No.
People are meant to carry
the burdens assigned to them.
We all have to carry our own cross.
That's the weight of life.
My friends' moms
always carry their bags
as soon as they come pick them up.
There. Happy?
Ma'am.
-Hello.
Is someone sick?
Oh. your kid's sick.
-Oh. dear.
-Hello.
Do you have a fever?
I hope you get better soon.
Ma'am. President Park
didn't come to work today.
Do you know where he went?
-Well…
-Hello. ma'am.
-Hello.
-We'll get going.
-Sure.
-Bye.
-Get well soon.
Bye.
Ha-jeong.
This is my office. Come here.
You know.
I was so shocked by your performance.
I have so many questions.
How did you find out
about the heating bills?
Right. You found the relics too.
Are you just good at finding stuff?
But those relics were authentic.
Where did you get those from?
It must have cost a fortune.
Right.
I prepared a small gift for you. Mr. Park.
Do you want to see? Come on.
Here.
Come on.
Ta-da.
It was hard choosing which photo to frame
since you looked good
in every one of them.
Do you like it?
But I don't like it.
I should've gotten a clear shot
of the disappointed look on your face
when you heard the bank balance.
He knows everything.
Are you really…
the president of Taesan Construction?
Right.
I haven't introduced myself properly.
I'm the president of Taesan Construction.
Lee Chung-won.
I'm Lee Chung-won from Building 123.
We'll…
be seeing each other again.
You seem to be great at finding things.
so what are you looking for here
at Taesan Group?
Whatever it is. I'm afraid
you won't be able to find it here.
I feel sorry about that.
No. I've already found it.
Why don't you…
let me become your right-hand man?
THE APARTMENT JOB
I'll do whatever it takes to support you.
Ha-jeong. just go live your own life.
Ms. Kang. were you crying?
Mr. Park. please let me stay the night.
A love story?
President Seo was the keeper of my vault.
I'm going to become
Lee Chung-won's vault keeper.
-Let's go meet President Seo first.
-President Seo?
-He went on a trip abroad?
-I don't know.
He betrayed us.
Release Yong-man on medical bail first.
Bring the cash. then we'll talk.
It seems Chief Son
is holding Park Yong-man hostage.
So that's why Park Hae-kang
needed the money.
Boss. becoming Lee Chung-won's
vault keeper is dangerous.
Do you trust Park Hae-kang?
I'm going to put him to the test.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park